// ============== - CountryFlags for testing================  
export default {
  id: 'general-knowledge-countryflags',
  title: 'Country Flags',
  timeLimit: 30,
  topic: "Country Flags",
  questions: [
    {
      question: "United States",
      options: ["US"],
      correctAnswer: "US",
      answerImage: "ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸"
    },
    {
      question: "United Kingdom",
      options: ["UK"],
      correctAnswer: "UK",
      answerImage: "ðŸ‡¬ðŸ‡§"
    },
    {
      question: "France",
      options: ["FR"],
      correctAnswer: "FR",
      answerImage: "ðŸ‡«ðŸ‡·"
    },
    {
      question: "Germany",
      options: ["DE"],
      correctAnswer: "DE",
      answerImage: "ðŸ‡©ðŸ‡ª"
    },
    {
      question: "Japan",
      options: ["JP"],
      correctAnswer: "JP",
      answerImage: "ðŸ‡¯ðŸ‡µ"
    },
    {
      question: "Brazil",
      options: ["BR"],
      correctAnswer: "BR",
      answerImage: "ðŸ‡§ðŸ‡·"
    },
    {
      question: "Canada",
      options: ["CA"],
      correctAnswer: "CA",
      answerImage: "ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡¦"
    },
    {
      question: "Australia",
      options: ["AU"],
      correctAnswer: "AU",
      answerImage: "ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡º"
    },
    {
      question: "India",
      options: ["IN"],
      correctAnswer: "IN",
      answerImage: "ðŸ‡®ðŸ‡³"
    },
    {
      question: "China",
      options: ["CN"],
      correctAnswer: "CN",
      answerImage: "ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡³"
    }
  ]
}
